spikedmath.com 2014-11-23

# Spiked Math - Privacy Policy

* * *

**Privacy Policy**

**Privacy Policy for SpikedMath.com**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at SpikedMath (at) gmail.com. 

At Spiked Math, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected by Spiked Math and how it is used. 

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, Spiked Math makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track userâ€™s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**   
Spiked Math might use cookies for the commenting system. 

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**   
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Spiked Math.  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to Spiked Math and other sites on the Internet.   
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include .... 

** Google Adsense  
** Lijit  
** Blogads

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Spiked Math send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

Spiked Math has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Spiked Math's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

**Lijit Information**   
Our advertising partner Lijit only collects anonymous information from you unless you choose otherwise. Lijit does permit you to opt out of the collection of this anonymous site visit data. For more information on opting out please visit: <http://www.lijit.com/choices> and select the Opt Out Now button. For more information on Lijit's privacy practices please visit: <http://www.lijit.com/company/privacy-policy>
